<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on David Burgstaller</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on David Burgstaller</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 18:47:54 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Devlog 1: Why I’m Creating This Game</title><link>/posts/devlog1/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 18:47:54 +0200</pubDate><guid>/posts/devlog1/</guid><description>&lt;p>My game project will be introduced in the next devlog. In this one, I’d like to share a bit about why I started this project and the journey that led me here.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I started programming when I was 13 years old. Even then, I was fascinated by the idea of creating games, which led me to learn C++, the programming language commonly used for game development. From that point on, I knew I wanted to become a programmer. Interestingly, becoming a game developer didn’t immediately cross my mind — probably because the industry wasn’t as large at the time, and most games were developed in the United States. It felt as distant as dreaming about working in Hollywood.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Devlog 2: Project Introduction</title><link>/posts/devlog2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 18:47:54 +0200</pubDate><guid>/posts/devlog2/</guid><description>&lt;p>As you may have read in the last devlog, this game is a showcase project. My goal is to expand and demonstrate my skills in game development.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>With that goal in mind, I’ve decided not to create a fully-fledged game but rather a vertical slice of what could potentially be a complete game. As a solo developer, delivering a large amount of high-quality content is simply not feasible, especially since I’m also working full-time. For this reason, I’m focusing on the quality of the game, but I’ll need to limit the content, length, and complexity. The result will be more of a &amp;ldquo;vertical slice&amp;rdquo;—a &amp;ldquo;demo&amp;rdquo; with around 15 minutes of gameplay.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Devlog 3: First</title><link>/posts/devlog3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 18:47:54 +0200</pubDate><guid>/posts/devlog3/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>